https://smittysholdings.com/privacy-policy-2/

Skip to contentPhone: (954) 861-0366
Menu HomeAbout UsBroward Web DesignStarter WebsitesBusiness WebsitesConsulting ServicesWordPress Monthly Maintenance ServicesWebsite Security & BackupsSearch Engine OptimizationKeyword AnalysisInternet MarketingPay Per ClickKeyword Ranking ReportsLink BuildingOther ServicesBroward Graphic DesignBroward Photographic ServicesVideo ServicesFine Art PhotographyTestimonialsNEWSContact UsSmitty’s Holdings, Inc. respects your privacy. Our goal is to gain your trust so that you can make the most of your advertising budget. We will never willfully disclose individually identifiable data about our customers to any third party. Nor will we sell our registration or newsletter lists to anyone. Believe me, when I say I hate getting junk e-mail as much as you do.What information do we collect? How do we use it?E-mail addresses are required in order to register for some features on Smitty’s Holdings, Inc.. We do not rent out customers’ e-mail addresses to third parties for unsolicited e-mail communications.How does Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. protect customer information?All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.What about “cookies”?Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. respects each individual user’s right to privacy. Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. may place a “cookie” on the visitor’s hard drive in order to facilitate a user friendly experience. Cookies are small pieces of information that a Web site places on your computer’s hard drive for tracking purposes. Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. uses cookie information it receives by placing the cookie on user’s hard drive to improve the efficiency of website experience, allowing visitors to enjoy the website’s features, and for Google Analytics to gather non personal information.Will Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. disclose the information it collects to outside parties?Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Also, Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. may provide aggregate statistics about our customers,Â  traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Smitty’s Holdings, Inc., our users, or others.In summaryWe are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.Your consentBy using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Smitty’s Holdings, Inc.. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.No information should be submitted to Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. by children 17 years of age or under without their parent’s or guardian’s consent. Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. does not monitor the age of its user audience.Tell us what you thinkOur goal is to protect your privacy. To help us improve our privacy policies, please give us your feedback. You may e-mail us using our online form at:Contact UsBy working continuously to understand and meet your needs, we hope Smitty’s Holdings, Inc. becomes your trusted resourceHomeAbout UsBroward Web DesignSearch Engine OptimizationBroward Photographic ServicesContact UsPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseContact Us Today at
(954) 861-0366 To find out how we can help youDesignated trademarks and
brands are the property of
their respective owners.Use of this Web site
constitutes acceptance of the
Smitty’s Holdings, Inc.
User Agreement and Privacy Policy
